familydollar.com 2018-12-26

# Privacy Policy

_Last updated: April 11, 2017_

Welcome to Family Dollar (“ **Family Dollar** ” or the “ **Company** ”). Please carefully read our Terms of Use (the “ **Terms** ”) and this Privacy Policy (“ **Privacy Policy** ”) before viewing the remainder of Familydollar.com and any affiliated Family Dollar site (collectively the "Site"). The “Site” includes by definition, and this Privacy Policy applies to, the Site itself, and any web pages, interactive features, applications, widgets, blogs, social networks, social network "tabs," or other online or wireless offerings that post a link to this Privacy Policy, whether accessed via computer, mobile device or other technology, manner, or means.

Your use of this Site constitutes acceptance of this Privacy Policy, the Terms, and any other policies, agreements, terms and conditions contained on this Site. If you do not agree to all terms and conditions, discontinue use of this Site.

Family Dollar reserves all rights to modify, delete, or append portions of this Privacy Policy, the Terms, and any other terms and conditions at our sole discretion. We recommend you review this Privacy Policy from time to time during visits to this Site and note any changes before your continued use of the Site. Your continued use of the Site after we post any revisions to this Privacy Policy constitutes your acceptance of the revised terms and conditions.

## **1\. Contact Us**

Please visit our Contact Us page if you have any questions or comments regarding the Site's Terms or Privacy Policy. You may also write to us at:

Family Dollar

ATTN: Corporate Communications

P.O. Box 1017

Charlotte, NC 28201-1017

## **2\. Information Collection**

The Site uses various forms for users to interact with us and request information. We may collect personally identifiable information such as name, address, email, date of birth, and telephone number, so that we may process requests, but also so that we may enhance our services to our Site visitors, make each visit as pleasant and helpful as possible, and track trends and statistics.

Technology (Cookies, Pixel Tags, other): We use standard technologies such as a “cookie” and pixel tags to collect information about how the Site is used as well as other information such as location. A cookie is a small removable data file that is stored by your web browser on your computer. We use cookies to, among other things, identify your computer during a particular session, i.e., when you sign into the Site or post a photo or comment, remember the items in your shopping cart, and analyze Site visitor behavior. If you create a user account or otherwise join our Site, these cookies enable you to store your password for fast logon and other conveniences. We do not store personal or sensitive information in cookies. Most Web browsers provide you with the ability to accept or decline cookies, as well as to be warned each time a cookie is being sent. If you choose to decline cookies, however, you may not be able to take advantage of all aspects of our site. Pixel tags, also known as beacons or Clear GIF’s, help us better manage content on the Site by informing us what content is effective. Pixel tags are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, pixel tags are embedded invisibly on web pages.

We may use location information to provide store location information, optimize promotional offers, and attempt to personalize notifications, advertising, or other content that may be more relevant to you. 

IP Addresses: We collect and analyze traffic on the Site by keeping track of the IP addresses of our visitors. An IP address is the unique numeric identifier assigned to each browser accessing the Internet. An IP address, by itself, cannot identify you personally. However, when combined with other information provided by your Internet Service Provider (ISP), your IP address can be used to identify the computer originating a message.

We may also periodically obtain personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information about you from affiliates, business partners, or other third parties, which we add to your account or other information we have collected.  

## **3\. Sharing Information**

For the purpose of operating our business, we may transfer information between Family Dollar and our service providers who use that information to conduct Family Dollar business. For example, they may handle Family Dollar’s credit card processing, shipping, data management, e-mail distribution, market research, information analysis, and promotions management. We may also share your information to administer a Site feature. We provide our service providers with the information they need to perform their services and work with them to protect your information.

We may also share information with product manufacturers, industry research companies, and other organizations for their marketing or data analysis purposes.

In order to better understand your preferences and better serve you, we may combine information we receive and that you give us online with other information from Family Dollar sources, transactions, and communications. We may also combine that information with data that is publicly available and data that we receive from other reputable sources.

We reserve the right to share personal information you provide with legal authorities if it is, in our sole opinion, necessary to investigate, prevent, or otherwise take action regarding suspected fraud, situations involving threats or potential harm, or if otherwise required by law (such as by a subpoena, court order, or other legal means). In the event that we reasonably believe that you have violated any of the terms or policies governing your use of the Site, we reserve the right to use any information we have collected about you in connection with any efforts we make or made by any of our agents on our behalf.

We may share your personal information with other entities affiliated with us for internal reasons, primarily for business and operational purposes including any corporate reorganization, restructuring or other corporate change. In addition, Family Dollar or any of its assets, including the Site, may be sold, or other transactions may occur in which your information is one of the key business assets in the transaction. In such a case, your information may be one of the business assets we transfer. Hence, Family Dollar reserves the right to disclose and transfer user information, including personally identifiable information, in connection with any activity and/or transaction described above.  

## **4\. Social Media**

Family Dollar maintains an active presence on several social media sites. Any published activity feed about you on the Site will be made available to other Site users, and may also be made available to social platforms, such as Facebook and Twitter. Please read the privacy policies of those social platforms, because your Family Dollar Site activity published on those platforms will no longer be governed by this Privacy Policy.  

## **5\. Promotions**

We may invite you to participate in a promotion such as a sweepstakes or contest. Participation in these promotions is completely voluntary and you have a choice whether or not to participate. We may co-sponsor some promotions on the Site with other companies. If you enter one of these promotions, our co-sponsor may receive the information collected.  

## **6\. Children and Personal Information**

Family Dollar does not intentionally or knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we should collect personal information from a child under the age of 13 unintentionally, upon notice of such unintentional collection, Family Dollar will immediately dispose of the information. Family Dollar encourages parents, teachers and childcare providers to closely monitor children’s online activities.  

## **7\. Security Measures**

Information submitted via the Internet, including through a web page, e-mail, or mobile communications, is subject to interception or incorrect routing, and the Internet is not a fully secure communications channel. Please consider this prior to submitting any information to us via this Site.

While we follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is perfectly secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.  

## **8\. International Users**

This Site is operated, in whole or in part, from the United States. By using this Site, regardless of where you live in the world, you consent to have your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States, and allow Family Dollar to use and collect your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  

## **9\. Your California Privacy Rights**

Under California Law, California residents have the right to request in writing from businesses with whom they have an established business relationship, (a) a list of the categories of personal information, such as name, email and mailing address and the type of services provided to the customer, that a business has disclosed to third parties (including affiliates that are separate legal entities) during the immediately preceding calendar year for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes and (b) the names and addresses of all such third parties. To request the above information, please contact us via the Contact Us information set forth in this Privacy Policy. We will respond to these requests within thirty (30) days. Requests that come by other means may result in a delayed response.

California law also provides that California residents are entitled to know how this Site responds to “Do Not Track” browser settings. Like many other websites and online services, this Site does not currently alter its practices when it receives Do Not Track signals because there is no consensus among industry participants as to what “Do Not Track” means in this context. To find out more about “Do Not Track,” and for opt out information, you may wish to visit <http://www.allaboutdnt.com/>.  

## **10\. Unsubscribe / Contact Us**

We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you prefer not to receive information from Family Dollar or would like to update or change your personal information or preferences, use the Contract Us information in this Privacy Policy. However, Family Dollar may send you service-related announcements, and transactional e-mail such as confirmations and receipts, from time to time through the general operation of the Site or by e-mail. If you do not want to receive any e-mail from us in the future, click the “unsubscribe” reference in any e-mail we send you.
